Unknown: [clears throat] Well, I found the one black Lego.
Kenzo: It's not a very good, yeah, Legos I got.
Unknown: Yeah, all the black Legos are evil.
Unknown: When everything was just yellow, like you could make the case they're Legos, they're people.
Unknown: Right.
Unknown: When they started making pink, like white people Legos.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Okay. Yeah.
Delwath: [clears throat] It's true, there's something about the yellow that's like-
Kenzo: Yeah, that's like-
Delwath: Clearly nobody actually has skin like this.
Wellby: At least Danish people could claim it.
Delwath: Right. Danish people, [chuckles] right, correct.
Unknown: They could pretend like it's generic.
Unknown: Exactly.
Unknown: They should just make them all red.
Unknown: That would betray it too.
Kenzo: Oh my God.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Oh, here. Just sort of put odds and ends.
Delwath: The, um, the Friends Legos are actually a lot more...
Delwath: Charlie was into the Friends set for a while.
Unknown: Oh, cool.
Delwath: And they have a lot more variety of skin tones.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
Unknown: There's actually way less to build, really.
Delwath: Yeah. They, they're, they're not as the, the Minifigs in particular are very-
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: -static.
Unknown: [clears throat]
Unknown: Well,
Unknown: a little
Unknown: less bits and this worse.
Unknown: Yeah. Good enough.
Unknown: [coughs]
Wellby: Should we get like computers and stuff?
Unknown: I mean, yeah, you probably need your character sheets at some point.
Unknown: Probably.
Unknown: And I, Kong, I don't know if you ever picked up like a boon for Kenzo.
Kenzo: Yeah, I picked, uh-
Wellby: Did you add the other arrow to the D&D Beyond?
Unknown: I did.
Unknown: Okay.
Unknown: Wait, I haven't picked a boon for Delwath either.
Kenzo: Uh-oh. Well, you guys better do that.
Kenzo: I am doing-
DM: Write it times up for me or something.
Unknown: You were g- talking about the can't die one.
Unknown: Oh, the can't die one.
Kenzo: Yeah, yeah, yeah. That's what I wanted.
Unknown: Okay.
Kenzo: Yeah, the hit points one. No, but I picked that, didn't I?
Kenzo: And then, then, then we use it 'cause I absorbed like a bajillion hit points in the combat.
Unknown: No, that was just your, the, that was your-
Kenzo: Oh, okay.
Unknown: That, that was before you leveled up.
Unknown: You leveled up at the end of it.
Unknown: Yeah. Yeah, yeah. No, no, I want, I want, I want to-
Unknown: I got it. I'll add it to here.
Unknown: I need to decide between, um, um,
Delwath: teleporting and extra speed.
Unknown: Well, you better decide now.
Unknown: Wait, did you change the insects to be a bonus action?
Unknown: I did, but you can just change it back.
Delwath: No, I mean you would, you agree, you are willing to change it, 'cause that's what I was trying to decide between.
Delwath: If the insects is a bonus action, then I'd rather take speed because
Unknown: I can still-
Unknown: Oh, no, I didn't change, I just said you can use another bonus action.
Unknown: Oh, right,
Unknown: which is the same thing.
Unknown: Which is the same thing.
Unknown: Wait, the, was it fourth?
Unknown: No, you didn't want the one that increased your hit points.
Unknown: You wanted the one that you can't die.
Unknown: No, I want the one that-
Unknown: When you're reduced to,
Unknown: when you're reduced to zero hit points, you drop to one hit points instead and regain a number of hit points equal to half your hit point maximum.
Delwath: Is that, is that, that must be once per day or something?
Unknown: Once a... Yeah, once per long rest.
Unknown: Okay, I should get my computer I guess.
Unknown: Last
Unknown: stand.
Unknown: We'll just see. We'll look inside the...
Unknown: Was there a, what was that thing?
Kenzo: It had sort of like odd bits and bobs in it.
Unknown: We'll look.
Kenzo: Plastic tray.
Seeker: There's a lot more stuff. What do you need?
Unknown: I'm not sure what I need.
Unknown: Oh, okay.
Unknown: I'm a, I'm a-
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Yeah, maybe-
Unknown: Yeah, there's all, there's all the stuff.
Unknown: Oh, right.
Unknown: Yeah. So much more.
Unknown: Yeah, those are there.
Unknown: I forgot about those.
Kenzo: [clears throat]
Unknown: Schwartz, how many hours, like when do you do the Lego stuff in your life?
Kenzo: Like is it kind of like kids go to bed and then it's like, you know, me time, and then I do, or is it like, you know?
Unknown: Uh, it's a-
Kenzo: Or take the whole-
Unknown: Pr- pretty much just summer.
Kenzo: Summer?
Wellby: Yeah. Like I, when I went back to work in August, that's when all progress stopped.
Kenzo: Oh, do you have your sum- do you have summers off or?
Unknown: Uh, I have July off.
Kenzo: Oh, that's awesome.
Unknown: So when you have, when you have July off, like you're not, you're not doing any administering at all?
Unknown: No.
Unknown: Yeah, I mean, I'm like, I'm responding to emails, but.
Unknown: But what if, what if your flock is in need?
Kenzo: I'm sure, I'm sure life doesn't relax in July.
Unknown: Or does your ho-- does everybody just like relax in July and then like, you know what?
Wellby: Nobody died this month.
Kenzo: [laughs]
Unknown: Everybody just stay alive.
Kenzo: That's what I'm saying.
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: Yeah. My congregation.
Kenzo: Yeah. How, how are yours doing?
Unknown: Really well. Really, really well.
Unknown: Check's gone, if anyone's-
Unknown: [laughs] Looking sharp for commissions.
Kenzo: Mm-hmm.
Unknown: I'll give it the heads.
Unknown: You want loads?
Unknown: I'm, I'm trying to, you know, I'm, I'm making progress.
Unknown: I'm like, eh, you know.
Unknown: Holy shit. The Scandinavian sea creatures, you guys.
Unknown: Very good. Watch out.
Unknown: Oh, yeah. They're-
Seeker: It's kind of like half between gummy bear and Swedish Fish texture, and
Unknown: There's a question.
Unknown: [coughs] The, the epic boons really give you a plus two in ability score.
Unknown: Right. Because-
Unknown: [coughs] The ability score increase is entirely pointless at this point.
Seeker: That one, we're destined to keep together because apparently it has some important side effects.
Unknown: How do you mean?
Unknown: Like, for the specific character.
Unknown: Yeah. I'm about to run an odd scoring on that one.
Delwath: Right. It can, like, boost, uh...
Delwath: It can, like, boost, uh...
Unknown: What's it say?
Unknown: Uh, Mysterio.
Unknown: Huh?
Unknown: Mysterio.
Unknown: Ah.
Unknown: Who's that? Who's Mysterio?
Unknown: Some Marvel guy.
Unknown: Oh.
Unknown: Hmm.
Unknown: Those bodies are ones I sorted out because they're either duplicates of what's in the bowl or they're, um, not-
Unknown: Ah, got it
Unknown: ... items we need.
Unknown: So these are, these ones?
Wellby: Everything in that whole thing you're looking at.
Unknown: Oh, okay.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Maybe there's something useful, but...
Unknown: [coughs] Too late.
Unknown: [chuckles]
Seeker: Although, the Kenku body's in there.
Unknown: Or do you already have another-
Unknown: [coughs]
Unknown: ... wings?
Unknown: Oh, man.
Unknown: Delwath was dull in there.
Unknown: Yeah, Delwath was so bad.
Unknown: Way better than with the bigger mirror.
Unknown: Yeah, definitely.
Unknown: I'm happy with that.
Unknown: Del was angry.
Unknown: Yeah, I wonder what Wath would do for a character like that.
Unknown: No, I, I mean, I like
Unknown: it.
Unknown: It's intense.
Unknown: All right. Delwath can finally move fast.
Unknown: Speed of sixty.
Unknown: What, what were my boons again?
Unknown: You have True Sight, I think.
Unknown: True Sight.
Unknown: Was there another thing that I did?
Unknown: You only get one at this level.
Unknown: Oh.
Unknown: You maybe-
Unknown: Wish and Spell.
Unknown: Hmm. Right.
Delwath: Oh, wait. Did I take-- I don't think I took my spell.
Unknown: Man, I didn't really prep for this at all.
Unknown: You took Shapechange.
Seeker: Shapechange, right. Oh, am I-
Unknown: No, I guess I did.
Unknown: Did I reset the count there?
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Where are we?
Unknown: We doing a time gap?
Unknown: Yeah. Yeah, it's been, it's been, like, a while.
Unknown: A month.
Unknown: Let me see what happens.
Unknown: Okay, I have to actually think about my spells for a minute.
Unknown: Oh, yeah.
Unknown: No.
Unknown: [clears throat]
Unknown: Thank you.
Unknown: Okay.
Unknown: Tim, I don't see the fourth arrow from the Wayfarer's Bow.
Unknown: Is it something I need to do, like, refresh on my end?
Unknown: Huh. Let me look.
Unknown: Oh, you probably have to, um, remove it and add it again.
Unknown: I'm gonna surely change that to...
Unknown: Sorry.
Wellby: Yeah, I had to remove it and add it.
Unknown: Okay. So I probably have to do the same thing here.
Unknown: Hmm. Hmm,
Unknown: okay.
Unknown: [items clattering]
Unknown: [coughs] I don't
Unknown: remember needing this part of this.
Unknown: Advantage, increase the DC needed for a spell or other magical effect.
Unknown: It probably comes under attack, but I think-
Unknown: Wait, isn't that the-
DM: That's one of the risky ones.
Unknown: Oh.
Delwath: Anything except another spell is a risky one.
Unknown: Yeah.
Seeker: Well, how about-- Let's, let's just... What are the probabilities gonna be?
Delwath: You should... Well, first of all, Seeker always succeeds at all risky magical effects.
Unknown: Right. Mm-hmm.
DM: So thirty-three percent chance you never have to cast Wish again.
Unknown: Well, it's a bit less than that because you can grow some footage now.
Unknown: If I had, if I had one.
Unknown: Right.
Unknown: Is your inspiration for d20 rerolls?
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: No, it's a reroll of any die you roll.
Unknown: Oh,
Unknown: okay.
Unknown: So let's...
Unknown: Two sides at thirty-three percent is just one-sixth.
Unknown: Uh, yeah.
Unknown: All right.
Unknown: Is
Unknown: it one?
Unknown: Hmm. I wonder how probability works.
Unknown: So you have to fail both of them in order for it, for you to fail.
Unknown: It's not a third times a third?
Unknown: It's a one-third.
Unknown: No? Is that wrong?
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Right. Yes, it is. You're correct.
Unknown: One in-- one, that's practically impossible.
Delwath: Yeah. When did that ever happen?
Unknown: Never.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: You fail one out of ten times.
Unknown: Yeah. Yeah. And can never cast Wish again.
Unknown: And so eight, reframed another way, eight out of nine times, you're gonna be fine.
Unknown: There you go. [laughs] Yeah.
Unknown: Hmm. Wait, what level is,
Unknown: what level is Simulacrum?
Unknown: It's an eighth level.
Delwath: So, so and so so, why don't you just make a Simulacrum and then have the Simulacrum cast Wish?
Seeker: Because it doesn't get to make a wish spell.
Unknown: Why not?
Unknown: No, the Simu-- in order to break the Simulacrum Wish chain, if your Simulacrum loses the ability to Wish, cast Wish, you do too.
Unknown: Ah. Oh, wait, so the Simulacrum also has Wish.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: We used that last time.
Delwath: No, no, no, 'cause we used Wish to create the Simulacrum.
Unknown: N- n- no.
Unknown: Oh, no, we didn't.
Delwath: The Simulacrum used Wish for a illusory dragon.
Unknown: Right, right, right, right, right.
DM: And Seeker used Wish for a force cage.
Unknown: Right.
Unknown: All over the place.
Unknown: But yeah, if you're, if you or a duplicate or a clone or other copy of you loses the ability to cast Wish, you also do.
Unknown: Okay. That seems reasonable.
Unknown: Bottom line would be no, you never-
Unknown: Yeah
Unknown: ... use Wish, 'cause you just always cast it through the Simulacrum.
Unknown: It can get out of control.
Unknown: Okay.
Unknown: That was Candrosa's turn.
Unknown: Oh, we're good. You can start.
Unknown: Okay.
Unknown: I'm just, you know, [coughing] fucking around.
Unknown: So-
Unknown: Pretty good spell.
Unknown: [coughs] [clears throat]
Unknown: Where-- so I'm gonna-- so the Tollen notes that I wrote, the interview notes go up until stopping in Orenlas, where you spend a few
Unknown: days, you know, talking with,
Unknown: um,
Unknown: Arheste, the elf who had fought Apollyon, and telling her about what happened and, you know, checking in on the elves and stuff.
Unknown: Mostly just keeping them up to date,
DM: uh, about the events, some of which they had heard about through [[Graham]], some of which was news to them.
Unknown: [coughs] Are you-- I mean, there's nothing that says you have to fly to Isingue in order to cast Plane Shift.
Unknown: You can cast it from literally anywhere.
Unknown: So are you-
Unknown: Yeah, wait, why don't we just Plane Shift from here?
Unknown: So to do that, we'll be linking hands in a circle,
Unknown: specifying the target destination in general terms.
Unknown: So I should have to search through how that-
Unknown: Can we just do-- ask the initiate before we go to Limbo?
Seeker: Well, [clears throat] there's some practical concerns related to teleporting
Seeker: that might improve our outcomes if it weren't for some, as though we were all inside a secret head navigating the ins and outs of the,
Unknown: uh,
Unknown: the definition of a teleportation circle.
Seeker: [coughs] That might be a Mike question.
Unknown: A teleportation circle? What about it?
Seeker: Would that be useful to have either on this side or the other side?
Unknown: Wait, I didn't think teleportation circles-
Unknown: Teleportation circles don't exist in Taelgar.
Unknown: Oh.
Unknown: Or potentially they do exist, but they are locked and requiring a magic that is not something we would ever possess.
Unknown: Is somebody making tea?
Unknown: I think it was water.
Unknown: Awesome.
Unknown: Um,
Unknown: all right, I'm...
Unknown: And the Wand of the Planes
Unknown: has seven Plane Shift charges.
Delwath: But Delwath doesn't have Plane Shift.
Unknown: Oh, okay.
Delwath: 'Cause I didn't switch it out. I mean, I was thinking about switching it out for Forcecage, but I didn't 'cause it was like, but how are you gonna cast Plane Shift?
Delwath: But I guess I could switch it out for Forcecage, and then you could use your wand.
Unknown: Yeah. [clears throat] As long as we don't need to go back and forth a lot.
Unknown: But I like kinda what I decided.
Delwath: Actually, I'm gonna-- I like the idea of Delwath having Plane Shift.
Unknown: All right.
Delwath: Delwath post this adventure is gonna be wandering around the plane, so he needs Plane Shift.
Unknown: Oh, shit.
Unknown: Ooh, live adventure?
Unknown: Fuck yeah.
Seeker: So the wand has the ability to slice between planes.
Unknown: We learned from our research that
Seeker: the slicing with Limbo actually could make things worse,
Seeker: but that's in the area of the wound.
Unknown: We could make a new slice far away from-
Unknown: But that also destroys the wand.
Unknown: Oh.
Unknown: What, like us?
Unknown: Creating a-
Unknown: Slicing between planes
Unknown: ... creating a permanent...
Unknown: Ah.
Seeker: And also could catastrophically fail in a really fun way.
Unknown: So let's not do that.
Unknown: And then I forget what Banish, what Blink does.
Unknown: Blink and Banishment are both useful spells.
Unknown: They're just useful spells, yeah.
Unknown: Blink just basically makes you immune to any...there is a 50% chance that nobody can do anything to you
DM: because you transport into the ethereal plane when it's not your turn, and then you come back.
Unknown: Ah. But it is an action.
DM: It's just annoying because it's an action to cast and you have to wait for your turn on it.
Seeker: It's a great run away spell.
Unknown: Exactly.
Unknown: Are you getting music?
Unknown: Yeah, I think maybe it's just a little quiet.
Unknown: Are you the speaker?
Unknown: Oh, it's not
Unknown: connected to your speaker.
Unknown: That's the problem.